treasureislandmedia.com 2019-04-08

# PRIVACY & COOKIE POLICY

**PRIVACY & COOKIE POLICY**

The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy describes how TIM (Treasure Island Media), and all of its properties operated under these names, hereinafter known as "TIM," collects information from all end-users of TIM's Internet services (the "Services") - those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who pay fees to gain access to the Service ("Members") - what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members ("Users") have concerning the collection and use of such information. TIM requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**Revisions to this Policy**

TIM reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. The user should periodically check for any modifications of this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on the user's browser. The user should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the "last modified" date remains unchanged after the user has clicked the "refresh" button on his/her browser, the user may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the policy. A changed "last modified" date indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting.

**Personal Information TIM Collects and How It Is Used**

TIM collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites accessible through our Service. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected when we believe that such disclosure is required by law. Registration: Members are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information is collected by our credit card processors, and is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances.

**Online Shopping**

At some of our Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information. If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient's name, address, and phone number. TIM has no control over the third parties' use of any personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so.

If you order products or services directly from TIM, we will use the personal information you provide only to process that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

**Online Advertisements**

TIM displays online advertisements. We are not affiliated with these third-party websites and are not responsible for their use of information.

**Responses to Email Inquiries**

When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to TIM's websites, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. TIM does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

**Voluntary Customer Surveys**

We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary.

**Other Internet Data**

TIM also collects IP addresses, referral URLs, browser preferences, the user's registration forms, surveys, and communications transmitted through site applications. This information is used internally to track how users come to be referred to our Sites for the purpose of compensating our affiliates, advertisers, and other marketing entities. This information may be disclosed to third-parties. If we choose to disclose information to third-parties, this information shall consist of non-specific information regarding site traffic and statistics. TIM never discloses any customer-specific information to third parties unless it is reasonable to believe that doing so is required by law, a binding contract, a Court Order, or other state, local, or administrative regulation.

As a service to our users we sometimes provide links to various third party web sites in our email communications. We are neither responsible for the content on nor for the information collection practices of such web sites, nor do we control the privacy policies of such web sites. Their policies may be substantially different in this regard from TIM.

At times, TIM may enter into co-branding arrangements with other companies, and if so, an opt-in or opt-out question may be present to allow email contact from these companies as well. Their opt-in/out features are specific to each organization, but you should not receive email from these organizations unless you have indicated that it is acceptable. Before consenting to receive email from third parties, you should read their privacy policy and terms of use, if applicable, to make sure you are comfortable dealing with that company. As you can understand, TIM can not make commitments on behalf of other companies. All email from TIM partners who gain your permission to send you commercial email, will include an opportunity to opt out of future communications.

**What We Collect and Why**

  * **Account Credentials**

We require you to provide an email address, password and username to use our services. We may also ask you to provide your phone number for order notifications or shipping purposes.  These credentials are used to identify you. 

  * **Purchases**

We collect information necessary to complete purchases. This includes, among other things, your name, credit card information, billing information, address, telephone number, and email address.TIM does not receive or process credit card information directly. We currently use 3rd party services that are PCI Compliant in handling online transactions. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. With fraud prevention and detection service providers - for the purpose of detecting and preventing fraudulent activity. Such service providers may keep records of information provided and use it when providing fraud detection and prevention services to other users of their databases.

  * **Mailing Lists**

When you sign up for a membership, make a purchase on our online stores, or subscribe to a newsletter we collect your email address to send you TIM news, TIM Services updates, the latest information on products and services.

  * **Third Party Analytics**

We use automated devices and applications, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate use of our Website and the Services. To opt-out of Google Analytics, please go to:  [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptocout/). Please note that if you use a new or different computer, install a new browser, or clear your cookies; in that case, you will need to re-opt-out through the link above. We use these tools to help us improve our Services, performance and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies to perform their services. These third parties may collect your device ID, IP address, or other information about your use of the Services as part of the analytics they provide to us.

  * **Cookies and Log Files**

We collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. We also use cookies and URL information to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and which you viewed.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by online service providers in order to make their websites or services work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.

Cookies set by the website owner or service provider (in this case, Treasure Island Media) are called “first party cookies”. Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called “third party cookies”. Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website or service you are using (such as advertising, interactive content and analytics). The third parties that set these third party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website or service in question and also when it visits certain other websites or services.

**Why do we use cookies and other tracking technologies?**

We use first party and third party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Websites and Services to operate, and we refer to these as “essential” or “strictly necessary” cookies. Other cookies enable us and the third parties we work with to track and target the interests of visitors to our Websites, and we refer to these as “performance” or “functionality” cookies. For example, we use cookies to tailor content and information that we may send or display to you and otherwise personalize your experience while interacting with our Websites and to otherwise improve the functionality of the Services we provide. We also enable our users to employ cookies and similar tracking technologies in connection with their use of our Services in order to allow us and our users to track their subscribers. Finally, third parties serve cookies through our Websites and Services for advertising, analytics, and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.

**The four types of cookies above will be either session cookies or persistent cookies.**

**Session Cookies**. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged into the Website or Services. This allows us to process your online transactions and requests and verify your identity, after you have logged in, as you move through our Website or Services.

**Persistent Cookies. **Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer.  We use persistent cookies to remember your user information, preferences and activity, to enable us to provide our services to you when you next return to our Website or Services.  We also use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity, which may be combined with other user information. 

**Local Storage Objects**. We may use Flash Local Storage Objects (“Flash LSOs”) to store your Website preferences and to personalize your visit. Flash LSOs are different from browser cookie because of the amount and type of data stored. Typically, you cannot control, delete, or disable the acceptance of Flash LSOs through your web browser. For more information on Flash LSOs, or to learn how to manage your settings for Flash LSOs, go to the Adobe Flash Player Help Page, choose “Global Storage Settings Panel” and follow the instructions. To see the Flash LSOs currently on your computer, choose “Website Storage Settings Panel” and follow the instructions to review and, if you choose, to delete any specific Flash LSO.

**Storage HTML5 Storage.   **We may also store your user information and Website preferences locally within your web browser via HTML5.

**Clear GIFs, pixel tags and other technologies**. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags), in connection with our Website or Services to, among other things, track the activities of Website visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about Website and Services usage. We and our third-party service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML emails to our customers, to help us track email response rates, identify when our emails are viewed, and track whether our emails are forwarded.

**Changing or Disabling your Cookie Settings**. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer you can edit your browser options to block them in the future.  The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.  Visitors to our Website who disable their web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Website; however, most site features will not function if you disable cookies and you will not be able to login to use our services.

**Our Commitment to Children's Protection**

Our sites are designed for adults, and not for use by anyone under the age of 18.

We have no Web pages designed for younger users. We make every effort to ensure that our Web sites contain adequate warnings to make their content obvious and to warn users under the age of 18 that they are not welcome to view our Web sites, we believe that there is no substitute for proper parental supervision of their children's internet use. Nevertheless, we will take any steps possible to discourage those under the age of 18 from visiting our Web sites.

If you choose to subscribe to one of TIM's websites as a "Member," your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information, and IP address are stored by our billing company. This site is an external entity, and once this information is transmitted to them we are under no obligation to police their use of the information, and take no steps to do so. All of the aforementioned information, with the exception of your credit card information, is also stored on our servers.

**TIM's Commitment to Data Security**

Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals we are unable to guarantee that our security is 100% breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite our reasonable security measures.

**Where to Direct Questions about TIM's Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact our Customer Service Department at [legal@treasureislandmedia.com](mailto:legal@treasureislandmedia.com?subject=Privacy%20and%20Cookie%20Policy).

Last Updated: May 24, 2018
